Denitsa Toneva

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

■ denitza.toneva@gmail.com

O Sofia, Bulgaria

Profile

As a driven and detail-oriented front-end developer with several months of experience, I have developed a solid understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and have been able to utilize my knowledge to build engaging user interfaces. Through my work with various front-end frameworks, including React, I have developed a keen eye for design and an ability to solve complex problems in a creative and efficient manner. I am committed to staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies and am confident in my ability to contribute to any development project.

Experience

Novarto Front-End Academy Trainee, Novarto Ltd., Sofia

July 2023 — December 2023

- Developed web applications using React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Worked on features which consume REST APIs
- Communicated with other team members regarding project status and issues as they arise
- Collaborated with project managers and development team to brainstorm new ideas
- Attended development programs to gain competencies and boost skills set
- Shadowed developers to learn key details about job duties and tasks

RPA Developer, Service Centrix Ltd., Sofia

June 2022 — July 2023

- Built, configured and tested robotic applications for business process automation
- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere

Projects

E-commerce storefront

- Demo: https://e-commerce-dstoneva.netlify.app/
- View project: https://github.com/dstoneva/e-commerce

Personal website

- Demo: https://dstoneva.netlify.app/
- View project: https://github.com/dstoneva/personal-website

Education

Mechatronics, Technical University of Sofia

2018 — 2022

Links

Personal Website

GitHub

Tech Stack

ReactJS

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Git

Material UI

Reactstrap